SKIP THE CLEANUP
Painting or sanding?
Skip hours of cleanup.
TAPE + FILM IN ONE
Pre-taped masking film combines yellow tape
and clear PE film in one roll.
TAPE FIRST
First, press the yellow tape firmly
along the cabinet edge.
PULL DOWN TO COVER
Then pull the film down smoothly
to cover the tile and countertop.
TEAR BY HAND
Fix the far edge, pull tight, and tear it by hand.
No scissors.
PAINT STAYS ON FILM
Paint and dust stay on the film,
not on your furniture.
PEEL CLEAN
Peel it away. No damage, no sticky residue,
and no cleanup.
FASTER MASKING. LESS CLEANUP.
One roll, faster masking, and far less cleanup.
Try pre-taped masking film on your next project.